Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
5488 B
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
669 linear feet.
Correspondence, Rule books, Agreements, etc.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
SUBJECTS
Names:
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
Subjects:
Railroads--Employees--Labor unions--United States--Sources.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted. Please contact the Kheel Center Reference Archivist for access information.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
This forms a portion of collection #5488 B. The guide to the entire collection is available here.
Series XCVII is arranged in 1 sub-series by Union file number.
Series XCVIII is arranged 169 in sub-series by Union file number.
CONTAINER LIST
- Series XCVII. AUXILIARY LODGES
  - Sub-Series 476-0. Auxiliary Lodges
    - General, 1947-1948 (Box 609a, Folder 1)
    - General, 1945-1946 (Box 609a, Folder 2)
    - General, 1943 (Box 609b, Folder 1)
      January-September 1943.
    - General, 1942 (Box 609b, Folder 2)
    - General, 1941 (Box 609b, Folder 3)
    - General, 1940 (Box 609b, Folder 4)
    - Auxiliary Lodges Chartered, 1940-1944 (Box 609b, Folder 5)
    - General, 1943-1944 (Box 609b, Folder 6)
      October 1943-44.
- Series XCVIII. 1943 CONVENTION
  - Sub-Series 477-0. 1943 Convention. General
    - Report of Grand President, 1943 (Box 610a, Folder 1)
    - Report of Grand Lodge Officers, 1943 (Box 610a, Folder 2)
    - Proceedings, 1943 (Box 610a, Folder 3)
    - Index of Resolutions, 1943 (Box 610a, Folder 4)
    - General, 1940-1946 (Box 610a, Folder 5)
    - Resolutions Submitted to Convention., 1943 (Box 610a, Folder 6-8)
    - Report of Grand Lodge Officers, 1943 (Box 610a, Folder 9)
    - Invitation of Brotherhood by City of St. Louis, Missouri, 1943 (Box 610a, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 477-1. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 1
    - Oppose Congressmen Who Attempt to Suppress Labor and Curtail Gains Made by Labor in Past Eight Years, 1943-1946 (Box 610a, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 477-1. 1943 Convention. Grand President's Convention Report
    - Report, 1941-1943 (Box 610a, Folder 12)
    - Report, 1943 (Box 610a, Folder 13-14)
    - Work Sheets, 1943 (Box 610a, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 477-2. 1943 Convention. Economic Security in Post-War Period
    - General, 1943 (Box 610b, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 477-2. 1943 Convention. Report of Committee on Legislation.
    - General, 1943 (Box 610b, Folder 2)
    - General, 1942-1943 (Box 610b, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 477-3. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 3
    - Bring War to Successful Conclusion and More Secure Economy Thereafter, 1946 (Box 610b, Folder 4)
    - Appeals, 1939-1943 (Box 610b, Folder 5)
    - Appeals. Menzner, W.W., 1940-1943 (Box 610b, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 477-4. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 4
    - When Officers of Brotherhood Are Accused of Violation of Company Rules, Brotherhood Officials to Be Permitted to Sit in Judgment With Company Official and Be Granted Equal Power, 1943-1946 (Box 610b, Folder 7)
    - Hotel, 1942 (Box 610b, Folder 8)
    - Hotel Carter, Cleveland, Ohio, 1943 (Box 610b, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 477-5. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 5
    - Local Chairmen and Other Representatives Shall Be Allowed on Company Property at Any Time if Such Visit is For Purpose of Seeing That Company is Living Up to Working Agreemen., 1943-1946 (Box 610b, Folder 10)
    - Non-Delegate Appointments, 1942-1943 (Box 610b, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 477-6. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 6
    - Additional Penalty For Work Performed Beyond a Full Day's Assignment On Holidays or Days of Rest, 1943-1946 (Box 610b, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 477-7. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 7
    - Carriers Should Be Required to Bulletin Vacation Relief Clerks' Jobs When Such Assignments Are For More than 30 Days' Duration., 1943-1946 (Box 610b, Folder 13)
    - Requests for Committee Appointments, 1942-1943 (Box 610b, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 477-8. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 8
    - Amend Article 45 of Grand Lodge Constitution to Provide for Referendum Ballot for Election of System or District Board of Adjustment Officers, 1943-1946 (Box 610b, Folder 15)
    - Grand Lodge Officers' Reports, 1943 (Box 610b, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 477-9. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 9
    - Amend Death Benefit Department Laws to Permit Naming of Persons Other than Relatives as Beneficiaries, 1943-1946 (Box 610b, Folder 17)
    - General, 1943 (Box 610b, Folder 18)
  - Sub-Series 477-10. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 10
    - Enactment of Federal Workmen's Compensation., 1946 (Box 610b, Folder 19)
    - Pullman Rates, 1943-1944 (Box 610b, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 477-11. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 11
    - Transportation for Delegates, 1943 (Box 611a, Folder 1)
    - National Sick Leave Rule, 1943-1946 (Box 611a, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 477-12. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 12
    - Committee on Finance, Salaries, Mileage and Per Diem, 1943 (Box 611a, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 477-13. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 13
    - Amend Railroad Retirement Act to Provide Disability and Sickness Annuity After 20 Years' Service, 1943-1946 (Box 611a, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 477-14. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 14
    - Secure Sick Leave Rules in All Working Agreements, 1943-1946 (Box 611a, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 477-15. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 15
    - Pension After 30 Years' Service Regardless of Age, 1943-1946 (Box 611a, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 477-16. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 16
    - Reduce Retirement Age From 65 to 60, 1943-1946 (Box 611a, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 477-17. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 17
    - Compulsory Retirement at 65 Years of Age, and at 60 After 30 Years' Service; With Minimum Annuity of $100 Per Month, 1943-1946 (Box 611a, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 477-18. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 18
    - Minimum Annuity of $100 Per Month, 1943-1946 (Box 611a, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 477-19. 1943 Convention. By-Laws
    - Kentucky State Legislative Committee, 1933-1949 (Box 611a, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 477-19. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 19
    - Increase Weekly Benefits Under State Workmen's Compensation., 1943-1946 (Box 611a, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 477-20. 1943 Convention. By-Laws
    - Louisiana State Legislative Committee, 1945-1949 (Box 611a, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 477-20. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 20
    - Retirement At 60 After 30 Years' Service, 1943 (Box 611a, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 477-21. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 21
    - Widow and Children Benefits; Disability Annuity After 15 Years' Service; Full Annuity After Age 60 Rather Than 65, 1943 (Box 611a, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 477-22. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 22
    - Carrier Service Only to Be Used in Determining Annuity, 1943 (Box 611a, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 477-23. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 23
    - Fifty Per Cent of Pensioner's Annuity to Go to Widow, 1943 (Box 611a, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 477-24. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 24
    - Negotiable Bona Fide Sick Leave, 1943 (Box 611a, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 477-25. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 25
    - Amend Railway Labor Act to Limit Waiting Period on Wage Negotiations, etc., to 60 Days, 1943 (Box 611a, Folder 18)
  - Sub-Series 477-26. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 26
    - 40-Hour Week With No Reduction in Compensation., 1943 (Box 611a, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 477-27. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 27
    - Employees Working at Night to Be Paid at a Rate of 10 Cents Per Hour Above Day Rates, 1943 (Box 611a, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 477-28. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 28
    - Vestibuling Express and Baggage Cars, 1943 (Box 611a, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series 477-29. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 29
    - Free Transportation for Express Employees, 1943 (Box 611a, Folder 22)
  - Sub-Series 477-30. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 30
    - Horse, Scenery and Unfit Cars for Express Messengers, 1943 (Box 611a, Folder 23)
  - Sub-Series 477-31. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 31
    - Lasting Worldwide Peace Based on a Well-Balanced Economy, 1943 (Box 611a, Folder 24)
  - Sub-Series 477-32. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 32
    - Use of Radio by Grand President to Educate General Public in Furtherance of Labor's Cause, 1943 (Box 611a, Folder 25)
  - Sub-Series 477-33. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 33
    - Equalization of Rates of Pay, 1943 (Box 611a, Folder 26)
  - Sub-Series 477-34. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 34
    - Revise Rule 68 of Express Agreement, 1943 (Box 611a, Folder 27)
  - Sub-Series 477-35. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 35
    - Revise Rule 22 of Express Agreement, 1943 (Box 611a, Folder 28)
  - Sub-Series 477-36. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 36
    - Equalization of Rates of Pay in Express Superintendent's Office, Long Island Division., 1943 (Box 611a, Folder 29)
  - Sub-Series 477-37. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 37
    - 36-Hour Work Week, 1943 (Box 611a, Folder 30)
  - Sub-Series 477-38. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 38
    - Revise Rule 19 of Express Agreement, 1943 (Box 611a, Folder 31)
  - Sub-Series 477-39. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 39
    - Remove Addendum A From Express Agreement, 1943 (Box 611a, Folder 32)
  - Sub-Series 477-40. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 40
    - Labor Representatives Be Permitted to Participate in Peace Conference, 1943 (Box 611a, Folder 33)
  - Sub-Series 477-41. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 41
    - 40-hour Week With Time and One-Half Thereafter, 1943 (Box 611a, Folder 34)
  - Sub-Series 477-42. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 42
    - Express Drivers and Helpers Not Be Required to Work Under Police Protection Nor Cross Picket Lines, 1943 (Box 611a, Folder 35)
  - Sub-Series 477-43. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 43
    - 40-hour Week for All Employees Under Jurisdiction of Brotherhood, 1943 (Box 611a, Folder 36)
  - Sub-Series 477-44. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 44
    - Double Time for Work Performed on All Legal Holidays and Sundays; On Regular 7-Day Assignments, Time and One-Half for Work Performed on All Legal Holidays and Sundays, 1943 (Box 611a, Folder 37)
  - Sub-Series 477-45. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 45
    - Revise National Vacation Agreement So All Employees Under Jurisdiction of Brotherhood Will Receive 12 Days' Vacation Per Year, 1943 (Box 611a, Folder 38)
  - Sub-Series 477-46. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 46
    - Secure National Rule to Provide that Carriers Be Required to Add to All Monetary Awards Interest at Current Rate From Date Claim Is Filed to Date of Actual Payment of Award, 1943 (Box 611a, Folder 39)
  - Sub-Series 477-47. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 47
    - Modify Present Pass Restrictions, 1943 (Box 611a, Folder 40)
  - Sub-Series 477-48. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 48
    - Revise National Vacation Agreement to provide two weeks' vacation for all employees covered by Brotherhood agreements, 1943 (Box 611a, Folder 41)
  - Sub-Series 477-49. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 49
    - Minimum guarantee of 8 hours' work per day, 1943 (Box 611a, Folder 42)
  - Sub-Series 477-50. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 50
    - Eliminate subnormal conditions on New York, New Haven and Hartford Railroad, 1943 (Box 611a, Folder 43)
  - Sub-Series 477-51. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 51
    - 40-hour week with time and one-half for sixth day and double time for seventh day of work, 1943 (Box 611a, Folder 44)
  - Sub-Series 477-52. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 52
    - Revise Express Agreement to provide payment of salary to Express Managers on mileage and hourly basis, 1943 (Box 611a, Folder 45)
  - Sub-Series 477-53. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 53
    - Equalization of rates of pay for performance of identical duties, 1943 (Box 611a, Folder 46)
  - Sub-Series 477-54. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 54
    - Revise Express Agreement to require Agency to place Express Messenger on trains carrying express in cars either open or sealed, 1943 (Box 611a, Folder 47)
  - Sub-Series 477-55. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 55
    - Stop farming out of Express Messengers' work to various members of train crews, 1943-1946 (Box 611a, Folder 48)
  - Sub-Series 477-56. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 56
    - Inclusion of Express workers in Canada within the confines of the Brotherhood, 1943-1946 (Box 611a, Folder 49)
  - Sub-Series 477-57. 1943 Convention. By-Laws
    - Wyoming State Legislative Committee, 1947-1949 (Box 611a, Folder 50)
  - Sub-Series 477-57. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 57
    - 44-hour work week with 48 hours' pay, 1942-1946 (Box 611a, Folder 51)
  - Sub-Series 477-58. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 58
    - Sick leave and vacation with pay based on seniority and not on class of work done by a member, 1943-1946 (Box 611a, Folder 52)
  - Sub-Series 477-59. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 59
    - Provide death benefit insurance for members' of Ladies' Auxiliary, 1942-1946 (Box 611a, Folder 53)
  - Sub-Series 477-60. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 60
    - Elimination of "excepted" positions, 1943-1946 (Box 611a, Folder 54)
  - Sub-Series 477-61. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 61
    - Grab irons or steps for refrigerator cars, 1943-1946 (Box 611a, Folder 55)
  - Sub-Series 477-62. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 62
    - Labor representatives on draft boards, 1943-1946 (Box 611a, Folder 56)
  - Sub-Series 477-63. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 63
    - Remove "white," "Negro," "colored," and "Auxiliary" from Constitution., 1943-1946 (Box 611a, Folder 57)
  - Sub-Series 477-64. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 64
    - New members eligible to vote for Delegates-at-large, 1943-1946 (Box 611a, Folder 58)
  - Sub-Series 477-65. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 65
    - Amend Railroad Retirement Act to compel retirement at age 65; permit retirement at age 60 after 30 years' service with full pension after 30 years' service, 1943-1946 (Box 611a, Folder 59)
  - Sub-Series 477-66. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 66
    - Time and one-half after 8 hours per day, 40 hours per week; double-time on seventh day of week, 1946-1947 (Box 611a, Folder 60)
    - Time and one-half after 8 hours per day, 40 hours per week; double-time on seventh day of week, 1943-1945 (Box 611a, Folder 61)
  - Sub-Series 477-67. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 67
    - Reaffirm policy set forth in Resolution No. 98 adopted at Toronto Convention, 1939, 1943-1946 (Box 611a, Folder 62)
  - Sub-Series 477-68. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 68
    - Standardization of wage scales, 1945-1946 (Box 611a, Folder 63)
      August 1945-March 1946.
    - Standardization of wage scales, 1943-1945 (Box 611a, Folder 64)
      1943-July 1945.
  - Sub-Series 477-69. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 69
    - Inclusion of excepted and personal office force positions, 1943-1950 (Box 611b, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 477-70. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 70
    - Post-war problems, 1943-1946 (Box 611b, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 477-71. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 71
    - Better coordination and cooperation efforts of Boards of Adjustment and Local Lodges, 1943-1946 (Box 611b, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 477-72. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 72
    - Competition and regulation of transportation., 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 477-73. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 73
    - More efficient handling of grievances and matters involving application and interpretation of agreements, 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 477-74. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 74
    - Off-job and On-job training program to meet war manpower problem, 1943-1949 (Box 611b, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 477-75. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 75
    - No discrimination against women employees, 1943-1949 (Box 611b, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 477-76. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 76
    - Health and safety, 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 477-77. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 77
    - Elimination of short-hour work, 1943-1946 (Box 611b, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 477-78. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 78
    - General, 1942-1948 (Box 611b, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 477-79. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 79
    - Consolidations, 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 477-80. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 80
    - Highway motor transport; bus terminals, 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 477-81. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 81
    - Intensive organization effort, 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 477-82. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 82
    - Air transport industry organization., 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 477-83. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 83
    - Development organization program, 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 477-84. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 84
    - Military service leave of absence for System Board and Local Lodge officers, 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 477-85. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 85
    - Delegates required to pay transportation to and from Convention to be reimbursed for this expenditure, 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 477-86. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 86
    - Anti-labor legislation. 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 18)
  - Sub-Series 477-87. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 87
    - Amend Retirement and Unemployment Insurance Acts, 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 477-88. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 88
    - Eliminate various classes in working agreements, 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 477-89. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 89
    - Make non-telegraph agencies available to Clerks, 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series 477-90. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 90
    - Restore Rate Clerk positions to Brotherhood jurisdiction. 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 22)
  - Sub-Series 477-91. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 91
    - Extend seniority district of Boise Lodge No. 1019, 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 23)
  - Sub-Series 477-92. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 92
    - Urge Senate to declare determination of United States to work for lasting peace with equal rights for all, 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 24)
  - Sub-Series 477-93. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 93
    - Endorse President F.D. Roosevelt for reelection., 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 25)
  - Sub-Series 477-94. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 94
    - Demand program to protect workers from unemployment and its attendant evils, 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 26)
  - Sub-Series 477-95. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 95
    - Provide for vacation payments to members in armed forces, 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 27)
  - Sub-Series 477-96. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 96
    - Seek legislation to maintain proper differential between wages and cost of living, 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 28)
  - Sub-Series 477-97. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 97
    - Eliminate clause "without additional expense to the company" from sick leave rule, 1943-1946 (Box 611b, Folder 29)
  - Sub-Series 477-98. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 98
    - Equalize Express rate of pay in New York City with higher rates in other industries, 1943-1946 (Box 611b, Folder 30)
  - Sub-Series 477-99. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 99
    - Demand 40-hour week, with time and one-half for sixth day and double-time for seventh day of week, 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 31)
  - Sub-Series 477-100. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 100
    - Claim Brotherhood jurisdiction of all agent and assistant agent positions at non-telegraph stations, 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 32)
  - Sub-Series 477-101. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 101
    - Reaffirms Toronto Convention Resolution No. 101, calling for punitive rates for overtime, Sunday, and holiday work, 1943-1947 (Box 611b, Folder 33)
  - Sub-Series 477-102. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 102
    - Grand Lodge to furnish annual financial statement, 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 34)
  - Sub-Series 477-102. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 102
    - Organizing campaign, 1939-1941 (Box 611b, Folder 35)
  - Sub-Series 477-103. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 103
    - Make State Legislative Committees mandatory, 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 36)
  - Sub-Series 477-104. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 104
    - Waive all dues of members in armed forces, 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 37)
  - Sub-Series 477-105. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 105
    - Grand President to insist on vote by Congress on Pending Workmen's Compensation Law and report progress monthly, 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 38)
  - Sub-Series 477-106. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 106
    - Change service requirement of Railroad Retirement Act in connection with physical disability to 20 years, 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 39)
  - Sub-Series 477-107. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 107
    - Eliminate the word "white" from Brotherhood Constitution., 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 40)
  - Sub-Series 477-108. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 108
    - Eliminate the word "white" from Brotherhood Constitution., 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 41)
  - Sub-Series 477-109. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 109
    - Require Lodges not having 150 members under one System Board to vote for Delegate-at-Large, 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 42)
  - Sub-Series 477-110. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 110
    - Establish State or Provincial Legislative Committees, Grand Lodge to contribute not more than three cents per member, 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 43)
  - Sub-Series 477-111. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 111
    - Endorse President F.D. Roosevelt as "peace-maker" even to the extent of a fourth term, 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 44)
  - Sub-Series 477-122. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 112
    - Request Grand President to continue efforts to do away with unsafe and unsanitary express cars, 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 45)
  - Sub-Series 477-113. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 113
    - Amend Express Agreement to provide 15 days' sick leave and 15 days' vacation after 2 years, 1943-1946 (Box 611b, Folder 46)
  - Sub-Series 477-114. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 114
    - Equalize rates of pay of mail handlers employed by railroads with rates paid by Government for similar work, 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 47)
  - Sub-Series 477-115. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 115
    - Serve notice for change in vacation agreement to provide two weeks' vacation and sick leave for all railroad employees, 1943-1946 (Box 611b, Folder 48)
  - Sub-Series 477-116. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 116
    - Establish higher rates for night work than for day work, 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 49)
  - Sub-Series 477-117. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 117
    - Liberalize the Railroad Retirement Act to allow physically disqualified employees full pension after 30 years' service, 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 50)
  - Sub-Series 477-118. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 118
    - Night wage differential, 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 51)
  - Sub-Series 477-119. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 119
    - Retirement permitted after 30 years' service, regardless of age, 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 52)
  - Sub-Series 477-120. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 120
    - Amend Railroad Retirement Act to provide minimum pension of $100; widow to get $100 until death or remarriage, 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 53)
  - Sub-Series 477-121. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 121
    - Demand 15 days' sick leave for all employees represented by Brotherhood, 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 54)